[Music]
yeah well that's why I can't be sunny
all the time a copy raining over time it
changes all the time it's all about
accepting things you cannot change
courage to change the things you can
then you have the wisdom to know the
difference but people live in fear and
fear stands for face everything can
recover a lot of people say your
breath you can run the other way it's
not a run you know start pushing through
the fears and I've done that a lot
through my whole life I actually get off
on it mmm actually get off on fear
because I know I'm gonna grow you know
it's just easier now don't do that oh no
I can't do that
then you said this will happen and
that's gonna happen yeah you know I
don't need to think about that stuff yes
what's gonna happen what happen I
learned that when my mother was driving
from Shepherd and back to Melbourne she
was driving in a car
there was a truck coming the opposite
way a spear will come off the truck she
swerved to miss it hit a tree and killed
her
straight up yeah and she was just
thinking about come back to Melbourne
yeah but that happened like that you
know things happen to people like that
all the time yeah so well we're in the
24 hours that were in and we said
earlier and we're here for a short term
yeah I remember when I was seven I feel
like my life's been a lot of chapters 7
16 28 and where I am right now
yeah so it's coming to that 54 now geez
what up when I was 23 and 27 and all
rest of it and a lot of those people
that I knew back then some of them
aren't here right mister continued to
keep drinking they're in institutions
jails or they did if you continue to
drink alcoholic alcoholic Li yeah or you
can come to a point in your life where I
was and something was I've handed
something handed that that will over to
something else and it was taken another
journey and I don't regret any of it I
don't regret the times where I was
drinking either but you have to know the
the good and the bad right yeah to know
what it feels like
you have to feel sad and happy you can't
be just happy all the time yeah they'll
be boring so it's just best like the U
and the yang now I think the yin and
yang is such a fundamental it's so deep
I mean that this is kind of like that's
that right yeah you you you walk out you
just stretch out into the world into the
unknown you just come back it's it's
it's in and out always and that's just
basis with basics of transformation it's
like animals when they'd fly the birds
the mother lets them go out they just
fly a little bit they come back right in
there fly then they just keep flying
right then they're to go on their
journey right yeah you know it wines and
fish and all sorts of stuff when this
berming they're going up they know where
they're going and whales and stuff here
they go all are in the world and certain
particular times yeah now that they're
in the flow yeah means ahead of the flow
we need to keep back on the flow right
yeah right to the flow coming into flow
yes
coming into flow and you know we see a
mindfulness revolution and meditation
revolution people are looking to access
this the ogre is being because it's just
yeah I think we're looking for at some
level I believe
mm-hmm yeah we're looking for unity but
is it this is there's a difficult thing
about unity because in some important
sense it can never be totally attained
because it's so it's almost like a dance
right
the dance is playing out a hole over
time but at any one moment you've lost
the dance you can't just chop it up it's
in the whole thing it's the whole song
right it's the full process of the art
it's the making of it and so one of the
I think this is another core existential
thing and I think a lot of difficulty
and suffering comes from this but I
think deep down because we are searching
for this unity I think sometimes people
get a glimpse and they think of what
they want to be and then they think how
could I ever attain that right there
they're wanting something final and
perfect but but final perfection is not
something that's attainable for us we're
in this constant relationship of making
and becoming right so so the constant
need to transform the fear that the
night will come that the darkness will
come that is the case oh yeah right but
we can come into relationship with each
other and that we can help each other
through and bit by bit we can make a
better world but it's it's never going
to be a final utopia there'll always be
problems there'll always be things to
solve is Raelians will rains will an ego
will always continue to keep going off
paths you stay ego wants to them to be
the man and they're the big people and
right now the Chiefs and all the rest of
it right but the true Warriors are the
people that lead their people in a
better way right a share and care and
will be with loyalty and honor and all
that stuff yes if
if a lot of us can start to learn to
live that way a little bit more yes I
think it'll be a better world
[Music]